Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events and Productions, 1982-1996, Undated; 2; 10.1 cubic ft.
  - Gay Games IV, 1982-1994, Undated; 2.3; 2.2 cubic ft.
    - Programs, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 10)
    - Progress Report, Boden Sandstrom, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 11)
    - Proposal, 1,000 Voice Chorus, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 12)
    - Proposal, Tom Ammiano, 1987; 1991-1995 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 13)
    - Proposal, Antigravity, Inc., 1992-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 14)
    - Proposal, Kerry Ashton, 1982-1987; 1990-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 15)
    - Proposal, Frank Aquino, 1992-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 16)
    - Proposal, B-Average, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 17)
    - Proposal, Suzy Berger, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 18)
    - Proposal, Laura Berkson, 1988; 1990-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 19)
    - Proposal, Karen Bilik, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 20)
    - Proposal, Sahir Blackeagle, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 21)
    - Proposal, Amy Boyd, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 22)
    - Proposal, Seraiah Carol, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 23)
    - Proposal, Doug Stevens and the Outband, 1991-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 24)
    - Proposal, Chrissanne Eastwood, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 25)
    - Proposal, Entry Forms, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 26)
    - Proposal, Maria Esposito, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 27)
    - Proposal, David Eye, Timepiece, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 28)
    - Proposal, Eventures, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 29)
    - Proposal, Sara Felder, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 30)
    - Proposal, Walter Fitzwater, Dialogue Between Me and My Virus, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 31)
    - Proposal, The Flirtations, 1991-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 32)
    - Proposal, Fruit Cocktail Cabaret, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 33)
    - Proposal, Kurt Fulton, Sodomite Warriors, 1990; 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 34)
    - Proposal, Karen Gerbig, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 35)
    - Proposal, Monica Grant, 1992-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 36)
    - Proposal, Dino Hodge, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 37)
    - Proposal, Hot Dish, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 38)
    - Proposal, Invert Films, 1992 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 39)
    - Proposal, The It Twins, 1989-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 40)
    - Proposal, Jimmy James, 1987-1990; 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 41)
    - Proposal, Ira Jeffries, Theatrical Scripts, Man Child The BreakClotel, 1992 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 42)
    - Proposal, Pam Kansas, 1992-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 43)
    - Proposal, Andrew Kelm, Black Birde, 1992 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 44)
    - Proposal, Tracy Kennedy, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 45)
    - Proposal, Lesbian and Gay Bands of America, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 46)
    - Proposal, John McGivern, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 47)
    - Proposal, Mike's Film, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 48)
    - Proposal, Mimi=Freed, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 49)
    - Proposal, Miriam, 1991-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 50)
    - Proposal, Bryan Murphy, 1991; Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 51)
    - Proposal, Holly Near, 1985; 1990 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 52)
    - Proposal, Faith Nolan, 1987; 1989; 1991-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 53)
    - Proposal, Thomas O'Neil, Judy at the Stonewall Inn, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 54)
    - Proposal, Kile Ozier, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 55)
    - Proposal, Monica Palacios, 1991-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 56)
    - Proposal, Stephen Patterson, 1990-1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 57)
    - Proposal, Janice Perry, 1988-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 58)
    - Proposal, Planet Q, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 59)
    - Proposal, Sue Popper, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 60)
    - Proposal, Promotional Material, 1994; Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 61)
    - Proposal, Radical Faeries, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 62)
    - Proposal, Georgia Ragsdale, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 63)
    - Proposal, Richie Rich, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 64)
    - Proposal, Eugene Salandra, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 65)
    - Proposal, Sister Dyke-Auto-Me, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 66)
    - Proposal, Jason Stuart, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 67)
    - Proposal, Julia Tipton, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 68)
    - Proposal, Linda Travis, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 69)
    - Proposal, Mark Truitt, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 70)
    - Proposal, Tryst, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 71)
    - Proposal, The Unarmed Poets, 1992; 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 72)
    - Proposal, Judy Valenti, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 73)
    - Proposal, Waiting for the Show, Theatrical Script, 1992-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 74)
    - Proposal, The Washington Sisters, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 75)
    - Proposal, Laura Wetzler, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 76)
    - Proposal, Marcia Wilke, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 77)
    - Proposal, Liz Winfeld, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 78)
    - Proposal, Laurie Wolf, 1992; 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 79)
    - Proposal, Worm, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 80)
    - Proposal, Wry Crips, Procedures and Guidelines, 1989 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 81)
    - Publications, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 82)
    - Seat cushion - Gay Games IV Opening Ceremonies, 1994 (Box 35 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - Seat cushion - Gay Games IV Opening Ceremonies, 1994 (Box 35 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - Sports Report, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 83)
    - Staff List, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 84)
    - Staff Pass, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 85)
    - Unity Week Calendar, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 86)
    - Worker List, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 87)
  - Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival, 1987-1995, Undated; 2.4; 1.2 cubic ft.
    This subseries includes records of the Reel Visions Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival in Albany produced by Michelle Crone with Judy Disco. This consists of correspondence, advertising forms, financial records, clippings of film reviews, fliers, programs, handwritten notes and schedules.
    - Advertising, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 88)
    - Business Cards, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 89)
    - Clare of the Moon, 1992 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 90)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 91)
    - Directory of Lesbian and Gay Film Festivals, 1995 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 92)
    - Dream Girls, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 93)
    - Film Lists, 1993; Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 94)
    - Flyers, Programs, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 95)
    - Flyers, Programs, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 96)
    - Flyers, Programs, 1995 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 97)
    - The Killer Condom, 1991 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 98)
    - Mailing List, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 99)
    - Movie Promotional Material, 1987; 1994; Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 100)
    - New Clippings, 1991 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 101)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 102)
    - Out Here, 1991-1992 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 103)
    - Over Our Dead Bodies, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 104)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 105)
    - Poster (16in by 20in), 1991 (Oversized 5, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1982-1985, Undated; 2.5; 0.2 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains records of Michelle Crone's role as a Co-ordinator of the Michigan Womyn's Music Festival. This includes correspondence, fliers, programs, and handwritten notes.
    - Coordinator Union Negotiating Team, Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 110)
    - Coordinator Union Negotiating Team, Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1982-1985 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 111)
    - Coordinator Union Negotiating Team, Meeting Notebooks, 1983 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 112)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1982-1985 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1982; 1985-1987; 1989-1991 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, Undated (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 3)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - T-shirt - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1981 August (Oversized 8, Folder 3)
  - Rhythm Fest, 1989-1996, Undated; 2.6; 4.8 cubic ft.
    Festivals ordered by date, undated material at the end, then alphabetical by subject
    This subseries consists of the administrative records of the production of Rhythm Fest, a women's music festival that ran from 1990 to 1996. Michelle Crone was one of the original five producers of the festival and was a key part of its origination after her experience at similar festivals. Present are correspondence, handwritten notes, meeting minutes, contracts, photographs of potential sites, programs, registration forms, evaluation and feedback forms, work exchange forms, and ephemera.
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Artists (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Coordinating Lists (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Coordinators Notebook, 1990-1991 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 9)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Evaluation Form (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 10)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Financial Records, 1990-1991 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 11)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest - Hat, "Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics", Undated (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest - Large canvas, many drawings and writings (50in by 92in) (Box 28 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Lease Agreement (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 12)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Location Search, 1989 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 13)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Meeting Notes (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 14)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 15)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Radios (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 16)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Shareholders Agreement (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 17)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Supplies (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 18)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt design on felt, Rhythm Fest '90: Women's Music, Art & Politics, "Beautiful! What do you think?" (Oversized 3, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt design on felt, Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics, "Surprise! This one is beautiful too", Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 8)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt, Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics, Undated (Box 22 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Vendor List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 19)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Craft area, Sylvia Toffel dances, Michelle C.[Crone], Garbage, Juggling etc., Mary Gemini with Barbara Marino, Alix Dobkin MC (1 of 6) (Vhs 13)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Sunrise, Kay Hagan, Texas Two-Steppin' (2 of 6) (Vhs 14)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Texas 2-Step Play, Sandia Lambert on disability, Alix Dobkin in concert, Michelle C.[Crone], Raffettes, Morgana dances day stage (3 of 6) (Vhs 15)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Morjana dancing, Mandy workshop, Morgana interview, Night Stage Tech Crew, organizers, Lea Delaria (4 of 6) (Vhs 16)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Lea Delaria, Casselberry-DuPree, Monica Grant (5 of 6) (Vhs 17)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Video - Monica Grant, Lea D.[Delaria] as MC, Girls in the Nose (6 of 6) (Vhs 18)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Worker Exchange Contracts (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 20)
    - 1990 Rhythm Fest, Worker Lists (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 21)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 22)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence with Herzog, Engstrom and Koplovitz, P.C., 1992 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 23)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Craftswoman List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 24)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Employees (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 25)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Evaluation Forms (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 26)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Financial Statements (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 27)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Flyers (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 28)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Inventory (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 29)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Lease Agreement (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 30)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Mailing List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 31)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Meeting Minutes and Notes (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 32)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Memorabilia (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 33)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Menus (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 34)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Newsletter (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 35)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Notebooks, Undated (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 36)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Notes, Undated (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 37)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Performer List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 38)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Photographs (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 39)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 40)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Rumor and Feedback Notebooks (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 41)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt design on felt, Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics (Oversized 3, Folder 7)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt, Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics (Box 22 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Suggestions (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 42)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Work Exchange Applications (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 43)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Work Exchange Contracts (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 44)
    - 1991 Rhythm Fest, Worker Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 45)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 46)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Evaluation Forms (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 47)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 48)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Flyers (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 49)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Inventory (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 50)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Land Crew (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 51)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Lease Agreement (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 52)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Media Marketing List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 53)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Meeting Notes (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 54)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Naked Controversy (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 55)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Notes (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 56)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Photographs (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 57)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Press Releases (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 58)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 59)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Radios (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 60)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Registration (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 61)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Report on Water (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 62)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Staff Communication Log (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 63)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt, 3rd Annual Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics, Undated (Box 22 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Worker Exchange Applications (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 64)
    - 1992 Rhythm Fest, Workers List (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 65)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Contracts (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 66)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 67)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Crone Photo (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 68)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Evaluation Forms (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 69)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Financial Statements (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 70)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Flyers (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 71)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Inventory (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 72)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Newsletter (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 73)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Performers, Leslie Kille, 1992 (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 74)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Performers, The Outskirts (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 75)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Performers, Kathryn Warner (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 76)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 77)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Registration (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 78)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest, Rumor and Feedback Notebook (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 79)
    - 1993 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt, Rhythm Fest: Women's Music, Art & Politics (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Advertising (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 80)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Articles (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 81)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Contracts (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 82)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 10 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 83)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Craftswoman Lists (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Evaluation Forms (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Flyers (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 3)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest - Large canvas, many drawings and writings (72in by 72in) (Box 27 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Lease Agreement (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest - Leather breastplate (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Memoranda (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, "Mistress" (Master) Sheets (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Notes and Financials, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Performers, Tracy Roso, 1993 (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Zenobia (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 9)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Producers' Workshop (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 10)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 11)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Registration Forms (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 12)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, "Rhythm Fest: An Astrological Picture" (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 13)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Questions and Comments Notebook (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 14)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest - T-shirt, Rhythm Fest V, Undated (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Video - "I.D. these women for me!" copy #2 (Vhs 19)
    - 1994 Rhythm Fest, Worker Evaluation Forms (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 15)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Advertising (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 16)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Assessment Project (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 17)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Cabin Assignments, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 18)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 19)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Evaluations (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 20)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Flyers (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 21)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Meeting Notes (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 22)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Program (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 23)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Worker Contracts (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 24)
    - 1995 Rhythm Fest, Worker Lists (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 25)
    - 1996 Rhythm Fest, Correspondence (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 26)
    - 1996 Rhythm Fest, Notes (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 27)
    - 1996 Rhythm Fest, Site Investigation, Notes, Photographs (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 28)
    - 1996 Rhythm Fest, Rumor Notebook, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 29)
    - Rhythm Fest, Cost and Material List, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 30)
    - Rhythm Fest, Elizabeth Doyle Writings, Correspondence, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 31)
    - Rhythm Fest, Land Notebook, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 32)
    - Rhythm Fest, Nametag, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 33)
    - Rhythm Fest, Notes, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 34)
    - Rhythm Fest, Performers, Julie Wolfe, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 35)
    - Rhythm Fest, Preparation Agenda, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 36)
    - Rhythm Fest, Ritual Abuse Survivors Booth, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 37)
    - Rhythm Fest, Sexual Awareness Notebook, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 38)
    - Rhythm Fest, Video - Film of Lookout Mountain Festival Site, Undated (Vhs 20)
  - Festivals - Other, 1982-1996, Undated; 2.7; 0.2 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains material that concerns other festivals or events that Michelle Crone was involved with in some way. The material consists of some administrative documentation, fliers and other published materials, handwritten notes, financial documents, programs, and contracts.
    - Global Gayity, 1995-1996 (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 39)